Downtown Gallery
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Correspondence, 1926-1974, undated, Series 1:; (Boxes 1-22; 22 linear ft.; Reels 5488-5545)
  Office of International Information and Cultural Affairs, 1946
  Office of Military Government for Germany (U.S.), 1948
  Office of Special Service Headquarters, Camp Kilmer, N.J., 1943
  Office of War Information, 1945
  Charles Z. Offin Advertising, Inc., 1947, 1951, 1953, 1958, 1960, 1962-1964, 1966-1968
  Ohannessian, Griselda, 1968
  Ohio State University, 1953, 1958-1959, 1960, 1963
  Ohio University, 1931, 1946, 1952-1954, 1958, 1964
  Ohio Wesleyan University, 1954, 1956, 1958, 1960
  Oi, Lam, 1967
  Oka, Wilfred M., 1968
  O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1946, 1952, 1954-1956, 1958, 1960, 1963-1964
  Okeley, Edward, 1940
  Okimoto, T., 1967
  Oklahoma Art Center, 1946, 1967-1968
  Oklahoma Printmakers Society, 1960
  Old Town Galleries, 1969
  Old Westbury Gardens, Inc., 1960
  Oldfield, Otis, 1931
  Olds, Elizabeth Fogg (Mrs. Lawrence B.), undated, 1963
  Olds, Ella Raines (Mrs. Robin), 1951
  Olin, Gladys, 1960
  Olivia Associates, Ltd., 1967
  Olsen, Fred, 1950
  Olson, Elizabeth R. (Mrs. Reuben L.), 1954
  Omaha Agricultural and Mechanical
  College, 1957
  Omaha Municipal Univeristy (see: Municipal University of Omaha)
  Omnibook, 1949
  120 Antiquities (see: Locher, Robert E.; Weyand, Richard)
  O'Neill, Marie, 1960-1961
  O'Neill, Terrence J., 1962
  Ontario East Gallery, 1966
  Openair Museum, 1962
  Oplinger, Curt, 1955
  Oppenheim Collins Co., 1958
  Oppenheim, Donny, 1962
  Oppenheimer, Arthur, 1946
  Pabst Brewing Company, 1953
  Paccassi, Virginia, 1946
  Pace College, 1958
  Pach, Walter, 1944
  Pacific Art Review, 1942
  Pack, Richard M., 1966
  Packard, Artemus, 1931
  Padawer Galleries, 1959-1960
  Paddock, William, 1962
  Padgett, Gail, 1967
  Paepcke, Elizabeth and/or Walter P., 1949-1951, 1953, 1957, 1966, 1968
  Page, Charles, 1962
  Page, Homer, 1962
  William A. Pahlmann Associates, Inc., 1964
  Paine Art Center and Arboretum, undated, 1964
  Paine, Ellen Lea (Mrs. Peter Standish), 1951
  Paine, Stephen D., 1962-1963
  Paitevin, Mercedes, 1969
  J. Pak, Inc., 1962, 1963
  Pakehita, Natenko, 1954
  Palette Art Co., Inc., 1952, 1964
  Paley, George E., 1959
  Paley, Lillian, 1961
  Paley, Mr. and/or Mrs. William, 1952, 1966
  Pall, David B., 1966, 1968
  Palm Beach Art Institute, 1962, 1964 (see also: Norton Gallery and School of Art)
  Palm Beach Post, 1965
  Palmer, Eleanor, 1965
  Palmer, Fred L., 1960, 1963, 1966
  Palmer, Hans C., 1964
  Palmer, Herbert B., undated, 1966, 1968
  Palmer House Galleries, 1958
  Palmer, J. Wood, 1956
  Palmer, Mrs. L., 1962
  Palmer, Mary C. (Mrs. Gerald J.), 1962
  Palmer, Roland S., 1930
  Pan American Union, 1950
  Pan American World Airways, 1958, 1964
  Pandolfini, Joseph, 1940
  Pantheon Books, Inc., 1954, 1961-1963
  Paplanus, Samuel, 1953, 1962, 1964
  Pappas, Louis, 1957
  Pappenheimer, Louise B. (Mrs. Ralph), 1949-1950
  Papsdorf, Fred, 1942
  Parade, Inc., undated
  Pare, Gladys R. (Mrs. Robert E.), 1953
  Paris, Robel, 1952
  Pariser, Susan M., 1961
  Park, Arthur R., 1956
  Park Gallery, 1951, 1960, 1962-1963
  Park, Julian, 1956
  Park Synagogue, 1961, 1965
  Parke-Bernet Galleries, Inc., undated, 1939, 1946, 1953, 1955-1958, 1961, 1964-1965, 1967-1968
  Parke, Samuel C., Jr., 1967
  Parker, Bill, 1958
  Parker, Inez Grant, undated
  Parker, James Reid, 1950
  Parker, Thomas, 1952
  Parkinson, Elizabeth B. (Mrs. Bliss), undated, 1950, 1955, 1957, 1959, 1962
  Parlett, Lynda, 1964
  Betty Parsons Gallery, 1961
  Parkway Triangle Construction Co., 1959
  Parnes, Sidmore, 1959
  Parrish Art Museum, 1946, 1956, 1966
  Parsons College, 1953
  Parsons, Harold W., 1945
  Parsons School of Design, 1961
  Part-Time People, Inc., 1966-1967
  Parzen, Dr. and Mrs. George, 1962
  Pasadena Art Institute, 1944, 1947, 1951, 1966
  Pasadena Public Library, 1958
  Pascal, E. L., 1965
  Pascal, Vern, 1966
  Passedoit, Georgette, 1961
  Paston, S., 1959
  Patterson, William J. J., 1952
  Pattison, Abbot L., undated, 1953-1954, 1956-1958, 1960, 1967-1968
  Patzig, Cynthia Lee, 1967
  Paul, Henry, 1951
  Paullin, Ethel Parsons (Mrs. Telford), 1956
  Paulist-Newman Press, 1969
  [Payson?], Helen, 1953
  Peabody Book Shop, 1930
  George Peabody College for Teachers, 1963-1965
  Peace, Bernie, 1965
  Peacock Memorials, Inc., 1958
  Peake, Channing, 1955
  Peale Museum, 1931, 1955 (see also: Municipal Museum of the City of Baltimore)
  Pear, B. Lincoln, 1964
  Pearle, Elsie (Mrs. Stanley C.), undated, 1960, 1962-1963, 1967-1968
  Pearson, Lucia S., undated, 1965
  Pearson, Norman Holmes, 1969
  Pearson, Ralph M., 1943, 1948, 1953
  Pease, Roland Folsom, Jr., 1960, 1964
  Peat, Marwick, Mitchell and Co., 1967
  Peavy, Paulina, 1952
  Pecher, William, 1969
  Peck, Augustus, 1930-1931
  Peden, Dell, 1959
  Pei, I. M., 1960
  L. E. Pelletier and Associates, Inc., 1968
  Pelligrini and Cudahy, Publishers, 1950, 1953
  M. Pelligrino and Co., 1963
  Penguin Books Ltd., 1963-1964, 1966
  Penick, Mary Monroe, undated
  Penn, Bill, 1953
  William Penn Memorial Museum, 1966
  Wm. Penn Publishing Corporation., 1957, 1966
  Penney, Charles P., Jr., 1963-1965
  Penney, James and/or Rachel, 1943, 1961
  Pennington, Mary Anne, 1965
  Pennsylvania Academy of the Fine Arts, undated, 1931, 1934, 1940-1948, 1950-1965, 1967
  Pennsylvania College for Women, 1952
  Pennsylvania Museum Commission, 1966
  Pennsylvania Railroad Company, 1947, 1965
  Pennsylvania State College, 1931, 1937
  Pennsylvania State University, 1955-1959, 1961, 1963-1965
  Pennsylvania, University of (see: University of Pennsylvania)
  Pennypacker, John, 1955
  Penobscot, 1966
  Pensanto, Joyce, 1961
  Peoples Bank of Johnstown, 1941
  Pepper, Ben, 1941
  Pepper, Charles Hovy, undated
  Pepsi-Cola Company, 1945, 1947
  Pepsi-Cola's Annual Art Competition, 1946
  Pereira, Irene Rice, 1945, 1965
  Perelman, Laura West, undated
  Perelman, S. J., 1956, 1965
  Peril, Barry R. and/or Marilyn, undated, 1964-1968
  Perin, Bradford and/or Nancy, 1941, 1967
  Perkins, Alta B., 1955
  Perkins, F. H., 1930
  Perkins, Philip, 1946
  Perkins, Ralph, Jr., 1952
  Perleman, S. J., 1938, 1942
  Perlestein, S., 1943
  Perlin, Bernard, 1946
  Perlin, Zalmar, 1951, 1953
  Perlman, Bennard B., 1962
  Perlman, Betty (Mrs. Aaron W.), 1961
  Perlman, Meyer, 1953
  Perlmutter, Jack, 1946
  Perlmutter, Victor, 1958
  Frank Perls Gallery, undated, 1942, 1949-1957, 1964
  Perls, Klaus, 1963
  Perper, Mark, 1934, 1942-1943
  Perrin, Madeline, undated
  Perry, Anna, 1964
  Perry, Donna S., undated, 1963
  Perry, Norman, undated, 1946
  General John J. Pershing Memorial Committee, 1954
  Perspectives U.S.A., 1952
  Pertzoff, Constantin A., 1953
  Perutz, George, undated, 1964, 1966-1969
  Peruvian Ambassador, undated
  Peshkin, Mrs. Milton, 1957
  Peterman, C. H., 1966-1967
  Peters, Alice, 1960
  Peters, Joseph, undated, 1964
  Peters, Muriel, 1941
  Peters Signs, 1940-1941
  Peterson, Charles, 1955
  Peterson, S. Marjorie, 1967
  Petschek, Stephen, 1962
  Peyser, Mark, undated
  Pfeiffer, Heinrich, 1933
  Pfeiffer, Ken H., 1951
  Phaneuf, Richard, 1964
  Phelan, Frances C., (Mrs. George A.), 1961
  Phelps-Stokes Fund, 1963
  Philadelphia Art Alliance, undated, 1931, 1939, 1942, 1947, 1952-1954, 1956, 1959-1960, 1964
  Philadelphia Inquirer, 1952
  Philadelphia Maritime Museum, 1964
  Philadelphia Museum College of Art, 1962-1964
  Philadelphia Museum of Art, undated, 1939, 1941-1946, 1948-1955, 1957-1963, 1965-1969
  Philadelphia Print Club (see: Print Club (Philadelphia))
  Philadelphia Water Color Club, 1950-1951
  Philbrook Art Center, 1939, 1941-1942, 1944, 1947-1948, 1952, 1962-1964, 1967
  Phillips, Mrs. Charles S., 1953
  Phillips Collection, 1951, 1953, 1964, 1967 (see also: Phillips Memorial Gallery; Phillips Gallery)
  Phillips, Duncan and/or Marjorie, 1930-1931, 1942-1943, 1951, 1954, 1966
  Phillips Exeter Academy, 1960, 1962, 1966
  Phillips Gallery, 1954-1955, 1957, 1959, 1961-1962
  Phillips, Harlan B., 1964
  Phillips, James, undated, 1956
  Phillips, Mrs. John G., undated
  Phillips Memorial Gallery, undated, 1931, 1940-1942, 1944-1947, 1949 (see also: Phillips Collection; Phillips Gallery)
  Phillips, Mrs. Seymour, 1959
  Phillips, Stephen, 1961
  Phoenix Art Museum, undated, 1959-1960, 1962, 1964-1966
  Phoenix Assurance Co., 1962-1963
  Phoenix Fine Arts Association, 1954, 1959
  Piaskowski, Nata, 1966
  Picadilly Gallery, 1962
  Picard Gallery, 1959
  Picher, William, undated, 1968
  Pick, Frederic G., 1952
  Pictures on Exhibit, 1940-1941, 1951-1952, 1954, 1956, 1959, 1961-1962
  Pictures Publishing Company, 1946
  Pierce, Ethel May, 1965
  Pietrzak, Richard, 1968
  Pike, Marion, 1955
  Pilgrim Airlines, 1968
  Pillsbury, Edmund, 1964
  Pillsbury, Mrs. John S., 1961-1962, 1964
  Pinchuck, Mrs. D., 1961
  Pinckney, Pauline A., 1939-1940, 1955-1956
  Pincus, I. N., 1959
  Pine Cupboard Antique Shop, 1953
  Pine Shops, Inc., 1951, 1953
  Pineles, Cipe, 1960 (see also: Burtin, Cipe Pineles)
  Pines, David, 1959
  Pines Publications, Inc., 1959
  Pinkerton's, Inc., 1965
  Pinney, Richard D., 1958
  Piper, Raymond F., undated, 1956
  Pipes, James, 1947
  Pipes, Raymond F., 1955
  Pippin Press, 1948-1949
  Piroumoff, Nina, undated
  Pirtle, Eugene, 1956
  Pitt and Scott Limited, 1962
  Pittman, Hobson, 1934
  Pittman Publishing Co., 1962
  Pitts, Anne, 1968
  Pittsburgh, University of (see: University of Pittsburgh)
  Plach, Eva R., undated
  Plack, Mrs. Louis E., 1947
  Paul Planert Associates, 1962, 1965, 1967
  Platel, Edward Charles, 1963
  Platt Steel and Supply Co., 1962
  Plaut Travel, Inc., 1959
  Playboy, undated, 1958, 1960
  Playhouse Gallery, undated, 1958, 1961
  Plaza Palette, 1959
  Pleadwell, Theodora H., 1946, 1954-1955
  Pleasants, Frederick R., 1961
  Pleasants, J. Hall, 1941
  Pleet, Gilbert, 1957
  Plimpton, George F. and Mary Wilcox, undated, 1931
  Ploch, Henry H., Jr., undated, 1964, 1967-1969
  Plymouth Rock Publications, Inc., 1958
  PM, 1940
  Pocket Books, 1953
  Podell, D. L., 1940-1942
  Pohl, La Vera, 1940
  Pohl, William M., 1931
  Poland, Reginald, undated, 1966
  Polier, Midonick and Zinsser, 1961-1962, 1964 (see also: Midonick, Millard L.)
  Pollack, Frederick, 1960
  Pollack, Peter, undated, 1941, 1954, 1956-1957, 1960-1964, 1967-1968
  Pollack, Sidney, 1942
  Pollak, Mrs. James E., 1966
  Pollak, Maurice, 1957
  Pollak, Robert, 1955
  Pollitzer, Anita, undated, 1954
  Pollock, Lawrence S. and/or Shirley, 1960, 1962-1963
  Polster, Edythe, 1961
  Pomerantz, Louis, undated, 1949, 1951-1953, 1961, 1965
  Pomona College, 1946, 1958
  Pond, Everett H. and/or Emily H., 1940, 1954
  Pool, Dr. and Mrs. J. Lawrence, undated
  Pool, James L., 1961, 1964
  Poor, Ann, 1956
  Poor, Henry V., 1927
  Poplack, William J., 1962
  Popper, Mrs. Arthur, 1946
  Popplereuther, Hans O., 1950
  Popular Publications, Inc., 1951-1953 (see also: Goldsmith, Harold S.)
  Port of New York, 1958
  Porte-Petit, J. Antonio de Villers, 1967-1968
  Porter, Cole, 1940-1943, 1945
  David Porter Gallery, 1945, 1951 (see also: G Place Gallery)
  Horace C. Porter Antiques, 1955
  Porter, Milton, 1949
  Porter, Sylvia, 1956
  Porter, Teresia B., 1961
  Portland Art Museum, 1939-1947, 1950-1953, 1956-1958, 1960-1961, 1963-1964, 1966, 1969
  Portland State College, 1958, 1968
  Portraits, Inc., 1960
  Portrayals of the Finer Arts and Span of Progress Exhibits, 1952
  Post, A. Alan, undated, 1942-1943
  Post, Mrs. C. K., 1940
  C. W. Post College, 1964
  Post, Diane, undated
  Post, Mrs. Jack E., 1959
  Postal Telegraph and Cable Co., undated, 1942
  Postmaster, 1942, 1961, 1963-1965
  Potamkin, Mr. and/or Mrs. Meyer, 1952, 1954-1956, 1965, 1968
  Potsdam State University (see: State Teachers College, Potsdam, N.Y.; State University Teachers College, Potsdam, N.Y.)
  Potter, Mr., 1955
  Potter, Arnold, 1963
  Potter, Bertha H., 1932
  Clarkson N. Potter, Inc., 1961, 1967
  Potter, Margaret, undated
  Potts, Ada G. (Mrs. C. S.), 1956
  Potts, Mrs. John, 1961
  Pousette-Dart, Nathaniel, 1953
  Powel, Mrs. Samuel, 1961
  Powell, Helen (Mrs. Charles), 1952
  Powell Floor Machine Co., Inc., 1940
  Powell, Mrs. Roe M., 1964
  Powell, Mr. and Mrs. Watson, n..d.
  Powell, Watson, Jr., 1962-1963
  Powelson, Harry, 1962
  Powers, John G., 1970
  Pozzatti, Rudy O., 1951
  Practicing Law Institute, 1956
  Praeger, Evelyn G., 1961-1962, 1964, 1966-1967
  Praeger, Frederick A., 1961, 1965, 1968
  Praeger, Mr. and/or Mrs. Leo, 1962-1963
  Prasso, Leona E., 1958
  Pratt Center for Contemporary Printmaking, 1967-1969
  Pratt, Dallas, 1959
  Pratt Institute, undated, 1958-1963, 1965-1968
  Premiere Art Gallery, 1961-1962
  Preminger, Otto, 1959-1960
  Prentice-Hall, Inc., 1956, 1962, 1966
  Presbyterian Life, 1968
  Presley, Jane, 1962
  Prestige Personnel Agency, 1967
  Preston, Catherine and/or Robert, 1963
  Preston, Flora Mobley, 1959, 1966
  Preston Gallery, 1962
  Prestopino, Gergorio, undated, 1945, 1958
  Preusser, Don, 1955
  Preusser, Robert, 1952-1954, 1960
  Previn, André and/or Dory Langdon, undated, 1959-1968
  Price, Edmund T., 1951, 1958-1959
  Price, F. N., 1945
  Price, Glenn, 1951
  Price, Maurice A., 1958
  Price, Vincent L., undated, 1949, 1956, 1959, 1962
  Pride, Robert G., 1961
  Primoff, M. W., Mr. and/or Mrs., 1958-1959
  Princeton Press, Inc., 1954-1956
  Princeton Print Club, 1941
  Princeton University, 1930-1931, 1934, 1960-1961, 1966
  Princeton University Press, 1955, 1959
  Pringle, Rosa, 1956
  Print, 1958
  Print and Drawing Society of North Carolina, 1964
  Print Club (Philadelphia), 1929-1930, 1935, 1951-1953, 1955-1958, 1960, 1961-1963, 1965, 1967
  Print Club of Rochester, 1935
  Print Council of America, 1957-1962, 1964-1965
  Print Makers Society of California, 1931
  Prior, Ann and/or Harris K., undated, 1958, 1963, 1965
  Prior, Roger W., 1931
  Pritchard, Edith M. F., 1959
  Pritz, N., undated
  Harvey Probber, Inc., 1958, 1965
  Proctor snd Gamble Company, 1958
  Progressive Citizens of America, 1947
  Progressive Packaging, Inc., 1963
  Promenade, undated, 1959
  Prosser, Hortense H. (Mrs.John), 1961-1963
  Providence Art Center, 1953
  Providence Art Club, 1955, 1961-1963
  Providence Lithograph Company, undated, 1968
  Provincetown Art Association (Incorporated), 1946, 1964
  Provincetown Art Festival, 1958
  Prown, Jules D., 1957
  Proy, Michael E., 1950
  J. T. Pryor, Jr., 1942
  Public Education Association, 1961
  Puerto Rico, University of (see: University of Puerto Rico)
  Pulaski Council of Milwaukee, 1946
  Pullitzer, Joseph, Jr., 1953
  Pullman Co., 1966
  Puma, Fernando, 1944, 1952
  Punte, G., 1963
  Purdue University, 1962, 1964, 1966
  Pure Oil, 1961
  Pushkin Fine Arts Museum, 1963
  Pustilnik, Mr. and Mrs. Jerome, 1965
  Putnam, Kingman W., 1949
  G. Putnam's Sons, 1935
  Putzel, Howard, 1940
  Putzker, Heidi and Ralph, 1951
  PWPA, 1936
  Pyle, Albert and/or Polly, 1965, 1967
  Pyle, Richard Temple, undated, 1951, 1958
  Quadrum Revue Internationale d'Arte Moderne, 1964
  Quaker Storage Co., Inc., 1966
  Quandt, Russell J., 1953, 1968
  Quarrie Corporation Publishers, 1946
  Quatre Chemins, 1930-1931
  Queens College, 1960, 1962-1963
  Quest, Dell, undated, 1965
  Quick, 1952, 1953
  Quigley Music Studios, 1952
  Quinn, J. William, 1966
  Quinn, John R., 1963
  Quinn, Ruth, 1965
  Quinnipac College, 1968
  Quintel, Lorraine, 1953
  Rabinowitz, Jarold W., 1953
  Ernest Raboff Gallery, 1963
  Alexandre Rabow Galleries, undated, 1952-1953, 1955-1956
  Racolin, Alexander E., 1958, 1960
  Radio Advertising Bureau, Inc., undated, 1956
  Radulovic, John, undated
  Radwany, Emery A., 1951
  Raffo, Steve, 1952, 1965
  Raiff, Stanley, 1959
  Railway Express Agency Incorporated, undated, 1945-1946, 1953, 1957-1958, 1960, 1962-1967
  George Rainbird, Ltd., 1964
  Rains Auction Rooms, Inc., 1934
  Raines Galleries, 1935, 1937
  Rainey, John, 1958
  Rainsford, Richard A., 1963
  Raker, Mildred, 1954
  Rambusch Decorating Co., 1955, 1958-1959
  Ramsay, John, 1942
  Rand, Mr. and/or Mrs. Jacob, 1945-1946, 1948, 1952-1953, 1957
  Rand, Nettie, 1949, 1951-1952, 1954, 1957
  William Rand, Inc., 1955
  Randal, Jules C., 1944
  Randall, Anthony, 1952-1953
  Randall, James D., 1961
  Randlev, Karen Ruth, undated, 1963
  Randolph, A. Philip, 1942
  Randolph County Schools, 1954
  Randolph-Macon Woman's College, 1946-1947, 1953, 1956-1965, 1966, 1968
  Random House, Inc., 1952-1953, 1956, 1963, 1965
  Randells, Neil J., undated, 1964
  Ransohoff, J. Louis, 1946
  Raoul, Rosine, 1964
  Raphael, Annette, undated, 1958
  Raphael, T., 1959
  Rapp, Carol, 1962
  Rappaport, Beatrice (Mrs. J. L.), 1950
  Rappaport, Roslyn, 1955
  Rapoport, Olga, undated
  Raskas, Bernard S., 1960-1961, 1964, 1969
  Rassmussen, R. Jens, 1961-1962
  Ratenburg, W. H., 1943
  Rathbone Books Ltd., 1959
  Rathbone, Perry, 1963
  Ratico, Ruth G., 1958
  Rattner, Abraham and/or Esther, undated, 1956, 1958-1960, 1962, 1964-1966, 1968
  Rattner, Lewis J., 1964
  Rau, Anne, undated
  Rau, Penny, undated, 1952
  Rau, Robert, 1959
  Rau-Kealy, Frieda, 1959
  Rausokoff, Mrs. J. L., 1940
  Ravin, Ellen, 1970
  Ravinia Festival Association, 1958
  Rawlings, John, 1947
  Rawson, Catharine G., 1956
  Ray and Ray, 1970
  Rayburn, Harold E., 1965, 1967-1968
  Raymond and Raymond Art Galleries, 1938
  Raymond and Raymond, Inc., 1945, 1950
  Raymond, Bernard, 1950, 1953
  RCA Communications, Inc., 1962, 1965
  Readers' Subscription, Inc., 1960, 1961
  Reading Public Museum and Art Gallery, 1950
  Réalités, 1965, 1967
  Reconstructionist, 1958
  Redbook Magazine, 1963
  Redding, Eleanor (Mrs. H. E.), 1964
  Redka, Eugenia, 1956
  Carroll Reece Museum, 1968
  Reed College, 1963
  Reed, Elizabeth (Mrs. John E.), 1953
  Reed, Isadora Bennett, 1965
  Reengum, Jerry J., 1952
  Reep, Edward, 1967
  Reese, Betty, undated
  Reese, Mr. and/or Mrs. Charles Lee, Jr., 1956, 1963
  Reeves, Ruth, undated, 1947
  Reeves, W. Harrison, 1966
  Refregier, Anton, 1960
  Regenstein, Helen M., undated, 1962
  Regenstein, Louis, Jr., 1960, 1963, 1965
  Register, James P., 1963
  Rehm, Mary Torr, 1958, 1967-1969
  Frank K. M. Rehn, Inc., 1955-1958, 1960
  Reiber, John G., 1943
  Reich, Sheldon, 1963, 1965
  Reichard, Myron L., 1963
  Reichardt, Jessica, 1962
  Reichhold, Henry H., 1945
  Reichman, Fred, 1964
  Reichmann, Edith, 1968
  Reid, Alma M., 1955
  Reid, Anne Cooke, 1960
  Reid, Mrs. Ira, 1960
  Reimer, C., 1960
  Reimer Inc., 1962, 1964
  Ethel Linder Reiner Productions, 1957
  Reingold, Gail M., 1964
  Reinhold Book Division, 1967, 1969
  Bernard Reis and Company, 1953, 1966-1968
  Reisman, Marshall M., 1957-1958, 1961-1962
  Reisner, Neil, 1965
  Reiss, Wallace, undated, 1952-1953
  Reitman, John, 1961
  Reliable Office Furniture Co., 1960
  Renaissance Society of the University of Chicago, 1945, 1948-1949, 1954, 1957, 1961
  Renders, Mrs. John F., 1964
  Rendle, D. E., 1965
  Rensselaer Polytechnic Institute, 1958-1959
  Charles H. Renthal and Company, 1967
  Reporter, 1953
  Resor, Helen and/or Stanley, 1935, 1938-1939
  Restrepo, Pedro, 1966
  Revel, Henry L., 1964
  Revere Copper and Brass Incorporated, 1934
  Revere Paper Products Corp., 1965
  Rex Envelope Co.., 1964
  Reynard, Grant, 1962
  Reynolda House, 1967
  Reynolds, 1960
  Reynolds, Harold F., 1947
  Reynolds, John J., 1965-1966
  Reynolds, Joseph N., 1961
  Reynolds Metals Company, 1959-1960
  Rex, Frances L., 1952
  Rhode Island School of Design, 1935, 1939, 1956, 1966 (see also: Museum of Art of the Rhode Island School of Design)
  Ribicoff, Belle and/or Irving F., undated, 1959-1960, 1964
  Stewart Ricard Gallery, 1959
  Rice, Dr., 1952
  Rice, Elmer, 1944, 1962-1963
  Rice, Marion, 1958
  Rice, Martin, 1953
  Rice, Maurice A., 1958
  Rice, Shirley R., 1960
  Rich, A. John, 1966
  Rich Displays, 1964
  Richards, Beatrice (Mrs. Bartlett), 1957
  Richards, Helen Hughes, undated
  Richards, Joe, 1961
  Richards, John Alan, undated, 1945, 1960
  Martin Richards, Inc., 1952-1953
  Richards, Rowland, 1946
  Richardson, Page G., 1954
  Richardson, Thomas L., 1963
  Richert, Bill, undated
  Richman, Robert, 1955
  Richmond, Anne (Mrs. Aaron), undated, 1959
  Richmond, Frederick, 1960
  Richmond, Larry, 1957, 1963
  Richter, Horace, 1959
  Stewart Rickard Gallery, Inc., 1960-1963
  Ridley, Emily Derr, 1943
  Ridley, Orrin R., 1963
  Rie, Robert, 1966
  Riesnfeld, Victor, 1953
  Riff's, 1953
  Riker, Jerome, 1955
  Riley, Eleanor Piper (Mrs. R. C.), 1950
  Riley, Marie (Mrs. Bernard J.), 1952
  Riley, Mary, 1955
  Riley, Mary Alexander (Mrs. Chapin), 1952-1953
  Riley, Maude, undated
  Riley, Verna P. (Mrs. Chester L.), 1965
  Rimmel, P. Grebe, 1956, 1965
  Ringel, Frederick J., 1954
  Ringer, Lotta (Mrs. Philip), 1954-1955
  John and Mabel Ringling Museum of Art, 1949-1950, 1955, 1957-1958, 1962-1965
  Ringold, Evelyn (Mrs. Herbert H.), 1960
  Ripley, S. Dillon, 1967
  Ritchey, Virginia, 1962
  Ritchie, Andrew C. and/or Jane, undated, 1960
  Ritter, Ralph L., 1956
  Ritz Associates, Inc., undated
  Ritz Tower, 1965, 1967-1968
  Rival, Freddy, undated, 1958
  River Dell Senior High School, 1964
  Rivers, Larry, 1967
  Riverside Radio, WRVR, 1960
  Rixey, Lilian, 1964
  Road, John, undated
  Roadside Art Gallery, 1959
  Robbins, Jerome, 1965
  Robbins Library, 1962
  Robbins, N.J., 1967
  Robbins, Warren M., 1961-1964, 1966 (see also: Center for Cross-Cultural Communication; Museum of African Art)
  Roberson, Edgar Paul, Jr., 1956
  Roberson, Genevive, 1964
  Roberts, 1937
  Roberts and Reimers, Incorporated, 1941
  Roberts, James M., 1955
  Roberts, Laurence, 1956
  Roberts, Mr. and/or Mrs. Michael, 1968
  Robin, Mary, undated
  Robins, Janet L. (Mrs. H. S.), 1959-1960
  Robinson, Andrew, 1962
  Robinson, Boardman, 1934
  Robinson, Carol, undated
  Robinson, Edward G., undated, 1934, 1942, 1945-1946, 1948, 1956-1957
  Robinson, Eleanor, 1937-1938
  Robinson, F. E. M., 1961-1962
  Robinson, Frances, 1935
  Robinson, George, 1944
  Robinson, Grace M. (Mrs. Romney), undated, 1955
  Robinson, Hazel Andre, 1963
  Robinson, John-David, 1959, 1961
  Robinson, Mary Turlay, 1952-1953
  Robinson, Sallie White, 1956
  Robinsons, Inc., 1958
  Esther Robles Gallery, undated, 1960-1961
  Robsjohn-Gibbings, Ltd., 1951, 1960
  Robsjohn, J. H., 1950
  Robson, Mark, 1950, 1960
  Sara Roby Foundation, 1962
  Roche, Martha, 1956
  Rochester Memorial Art Gallery, 1945-1946, 1954, 1957, 1959, 1961, 1963-1965
  Rochester Print Club (see: Print Club of Rochester)
  Rochester, University of (see: University of Rochester)
  Rock-Hil-Uris, Inc., 1963
  Rock of Ages, 1958
  Rock Springs High School, 1961, 1963
  Rockefeller, 1929
  Rockefeller, Abby A., undated, 1930, 1934, 1941-1943
  Abby Aldrich Rockefeller Folk Art Collection, 1955-1957
  Rockefeller, Barbara, 1955
  Rockefeller, Blanchette and/or John D. III, 1935, 1938, 1945-1946, 1949-1951, 1956, 1960, 1962-1964
  Rockefeller Center Galleries of American Art, Inc., 1933
  Rockefeller Center, Inc., 1932
  Rockefeller Center Weekly, 1937
  Rockefeller, Mr. and/or Mrs. David, undated, 1952, 1955, 1957-1958, 1961, 1965-1967
  Rockefeller Foundation, 1937, 1941, 1961
  Rockefeller, Mr. and/or Mrs. John D., Jr., undated, 1930-1933, 1935, 1938, 1941-1942
  Rockefeller, John D., II, 1955
  Rockefeller, Laurance Spelman, and/or Mary F., undated, 1935-1937, 1946-1948, 1950-1957, 1965
  Rockefeller, Mary Clark, undated
  Rockefeller, Mary and/or Nelson A., undated, 1932-1939, 1941-1942, 1944-1949, 1951-1952, 1955-1956, 1959-1960, 1962, 1965-1967
  Rockefeller, Winthrop, 1960, 1966
  Rockford Art Association, 1965
  Rocknem, Robert E., 1965
  Rodale Press, 1968
  Rodgers, William H., 1967-1968
  Roditi, Edouard, 1947, 1951, 1955
  Rodman, Selden, undated, 1945, 1947, 1951, 1955, 1957, 1959-1960
  Rodriguez, José, 1968
  Roebling, Mary G., undated, 1959, 1961